Guide to the Duke University Chapel Recordings, 1954-2002 UA.17.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University Chapel recordings
1954-2002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Cleland, James T. (James Tough), 1903-
Wilkinson, Howard Charles
Kammerer, Charlene Payne
Duke University. University Archives
Hall, Thor
Beach, Waldo
Duke University. Chapel
UA.17.01.0003
67 Linear Feet
Collection contains audio of sermons delivered at religious and ceremonial services in the Duke University Chapel by various ministers, professors, and guests of the University. Notable speakers include Howard Wilkinson, James Cleland, Waldo Beach, Thor Hall, Charlene Kammerer, Jon Laidlaw, Will Willimon, Robert Young and others. The collection consists of 7" reel-to-reel audio tapes, audiocassette tapes, VHS tapes, and digital audio tapes of sermons, programs and Lenten meditations delivered in Duke Chapel from 1954 to ongoing.
Related Materials
James T. Cleland papers (University Archives, Duke University)
Provenance
Received from various sources, 1970-present.
Arrangement
Recordings are arranged chronologically.
Online Items
Items from this collection have been digitized and are available in the Duke University Chapel Recordings - Duke Digital Collections
Historical note
When James B. Duke selected the site for Duke University's West Campus, in 1925, he chose to locate the Chapel on the site's highest ridge. The Chapel was the first building planned for the new campus, but the last one to be completed. Construction started in 1930, was completed in 1935, and cost nearly $2.3 million. The Chapel began to be used before its stained-glass windows and other details were finished; commencement was held in the Chapel in 1932. The Chapel was officially dedicated in 1935.
The Chapel fulfills James B. Duke's desire that the building exert a profound influence on the lives of the young women and men who attend the University. Duke Chapel is a nationally recognized pulpit, an acclaimed center of sacred music, and a place of learning and interfaith cooperation. Duke University Chapel's ever-widening ministry includes worship through prayer, word, and music; service within the University and community; celebration through concerts, special services, and festivals; and learning seminars, study groups, and retreats. The day-to-day ministry of the Chapel is shared with a wide and diverse community: students, faculty, staff, and the community; tourists and travelers; and patients, their families, and caregivers. Chapel life encompasses a variety of groups including Religious Life, Friends of the Chapel, Congregation, and Student Ministry. Duke Chapel is also the site of various concerts, voice and organ recitals, choir and carillon programs, and vesper ensembles.
Historical note adopted from Duke Chapel website: http://www.chapel.duke.edu/home/
Collection Overview
Collection contains audio of sermons delivered at religious and ceremonial services in the Duke University Chapel by various ministers, professors, and guests of the University. Notable speakers include Howard Wilkinson, James Cleland, Waldo Beach, Thor Hall, Charlene Kammerer, Jon Laidlaw, William Willimon, Robert Young and others. The collection consists of 7" reel-to-reel audio tapes, audiocassette tapes, VHS tapes, and digital audio tapes of sermons, programs and Lenten meditations delivered in Duke Chapel from 1954 to ongoing.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Use of these materials may require production of listening or viewing copies. Please contact Research Services before coming to use this collection.
The collection may contain materials to which the Acknowledgment of Legal Responsibilities and Privacy Rights form applies. Patrons must sign this form before using the collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Banner
Portions of this collection are off site for digitization and are not available. Contact University Archives for more information.
Audiovisual materials; Sound recordings; Videocassettes; Sermons; Cleland, James T. (James Tough), 1903-; Wilkinson, Howard Charles; Kammerer, Charlene Payne; Duke University. University Archives; Hall, Thor; Beach, Waldo; Duke University. Chapel
- Recordings, 1954-2002; 1
  Arrangement
  Recordings are arranged chronologically.
  - Toyohiko Kagawa - "Christianity and the Atomic Age", 1954 August 08; 1
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0001)
  - James F. Peter - "Troublers of the Nations", 1954 October 24; 2
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0002)
  - Rabbi Abraham Shusterman - "The Jew Speaks to a Troubled Generation", 1954 November 07; 3
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0003)
  - Halford E. Luccock - "Advent in a Distressed World", 1954 December 05; 4
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0004)
  - Canon T.O. Wedel - "The Mystery of Time", 1955 January 09; 5
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0005)
  - George F. MacLeod - "The Cross", 1955 January 23; 6
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0006)
  - Joseph Sittler - "The Faith - Situation", 1955 February 13; 7
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0007)
  - Paul J. Tillich - "Be Strong", 1955 March 13; 8
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0008)
  - Culbert G. Rutenber - "The Answering God - But How?", 1955 April 24; 9
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0009)
  - Roland H. Bainton - "Splendid Venture", 1955 May 08; 10
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0010)
  - Colin W. Williams - "The Lion, The Eagle, and The Vine", 1955 June 19; 11
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0011)
  - Albert Cook Outler - "Fit to be Free", 1955 October 16; 12
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0012)
  - Douglas Horton - "The Christmas Feast", 1955 December 11; 13
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0013)
  - Bishop G. Bromley Oxnam - "The Mission of the Church", 1956 January 15; 14
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0014)
  - Merrimon Cuninggim - "Freedom Is Commitment", 1956 January 22; 15
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0015)
  - Frank S. Hickman - "Out of the Depths", 1956 February 12; 16
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0016)
  - Herbert Gezork - "Discipline", 1956 February 26, 1956 March 07; 17
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0017)
  - Alan Walker - "A New Mind for a New Age"; "Jesus Christ - Savior", 1956 March 04; 18
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0018)
  - Alan Walker - "Life Has a Purpose"; Michalson - "Sociological and Psychological Dimensions of Unbelief", 1956 March 05, 1956 March 07; 19
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0019)
  - Alan Walker - Religion Emphasis Week, 1956 March 05; 20
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0021)
  - Arthur Jeffery - Sermon Untitled, 1956 March 18; 21
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0022)
  - Robert J. McCracken - "The Duty of Being Discontented", 1956 April 08; 22
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0023)
  - H. Shelton Smith - "Moral Crisis in a Troubled South", 1956 April 29; 23
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0024)
  - Douglas V. Steere - "On Holy Expectancy", 1956 September 23, 1956 October 07; 24
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0025)
  - James H. Phillips - "Power to Become"; Robert E. Cushman - "Holy Communion", 1956 September 30, 1956 October 21; 25
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0026)
  - James T. Cleland - "What Is This Christian Faith?"; Maldwyn Edwards - "God's Strategy", 1956 October 14, 1956 November 18; 26
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0027)
  - H. Shelton Smith - "Religiousness Versus Righteousness"; Creighton Lacy - "A Psalm of Gratitude", 1956 November 11, 1956 December 09; 27
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0028)
  - Harold Bosley - "Found by God"; James T. Cleland - Sermon Untitled, 1956 December 02, 1957 January 06; 28
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0029)
  - Robert E. Cushman - "The Time of Thy Visitation Vision"; John Baillie - "The Theology of Sleep", 1956 December 16, 1957 January 20; 29
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0030)
  - James T. Cleland - "Holiness and the Commonplace"; James Cannon - "Christian Faith", 1957 January 13, 1957 February 10; 30
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0031)
  - H. Richard Niebuhr - "The Hope of Glory"; James T. Cleland - "Long Day's Journey into Light", 1957 February 03, 1957 April 14; 31
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0032)
  - Eugene Carson Blake - "Even the Desert Shall Bloom"; Waldo Beach - "Education for Failure", 1957 April 07, 1957 April 28; 32
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0033)
  - James T. Cleland - Easter Meditation; James L. Price, Jr. - "Jesus Christ Is Lord", 1957 April 21, 1957 May 12; 33
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0034)
  - George P. Hedley - "Suffering Wrongfully"; Robert E. Cushman - "Divine Improvidence", 1957 May 05, 1957 May 26; 34
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0035)
  - James H. Phillips - "Profiles in Courage"; James T. Cleland - "Jack Coombs' Sermon", 1957 May 19, 1957 June 30; 35
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0036)
  - Bishop Gerald Kennedy - Baccalaureate Sermon; John Casteel - "The Prevenient Love of God", 1957 June 02; 36
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0037)
  - Van Bogard Dunn - "Living in the Proverbs", 1957 July 07, 1958 May 25; 37
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0038)
  - Paul J. Tillich - "The Flight from God"; James L. Price, Jr. - "Appearances Are Deceiving", 1957 November 17; 38
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0039)
  - James T. Cleland - "Triple Advent", 1957 December 08; 39
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 1, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0040)
  - Hugh Anderson - "A New World Beginning from Today", 1957 December 12; 40
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0041)
  - James A. Jones - "Beyond a Religion of Comfort", 1958 January 26; 41
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0042)
  - Creighton Lacy - "Fear Not, Only Believe"; Clovis G. Chappell - "Road to Greatness", 1958 February 02; 42
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0043)
  - James T. Cleland - "Let Us Pray", 1958 February 16, 1958 February 09; 43
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0045)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "The Tower of Babel", 1958 February 23; 44
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0046)
  - William G. Pollard - "What Is the Holy Spirit?", 1958 March 02; 45
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0047)
  - James T. Cleland - "Classroom and Chapel", 1958 March 09, 1958 April 20; 46
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0048)
  - Robert E. Cushman - "Lift up Your Hearts"; Waldo Beach - "The Anatomy of Integrity", 1958 April 13, 1958 May 04; 47
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0049)
  - Bishop Nolan B. Harmon - "No Wagons"; James H. Phillips - "His Only Son, Our Lord", 1958 April 27, 1958 May 18; 48
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0051)
  - Liston Pope - "With All My Thy Mind"; James T. Cleland - "Martha and Mary", 1958 May 11; 49
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0053)
  - Harold A. Bosley - "Pardon My Idealism", 1958 June 01, 1958 October 05; 50
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0055)
  - Ralph W. Sockman - "Prisoners of Ourselves"; James T. Cleland - Sermon Untitled, 1958 September 28, 1959 January 11; 51
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0056)
  - Waldo Beach - "High Time"; James F. Peter - "God's Rights", 1958 October 12, 1958 November 23; 52
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0058)
  - John Marsh - Sermon Untitled; James T. Cleland - "Rest and Be Thankful: A Sermon for Thanksgiving" Thanksgiving Service, 1958 October 26, 1958 November 23; 53
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0060)
  - W. Arthur Kale - "The Quest for Maturity"; McMurry S. Richey - "Communicating Our Faith", 1958 November 02; 54
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0062)
  - Creighton Lacy - "Horizons Incomparable (Incorporated)"; Howard C. Wilkinson - "The Church Looks at the World", 1958 November 16, 1959 February 15; 55
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0066)
  - Albert C. Outler - "The Lonely Crowd", 1959 March 15; 56
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0068)
  - James L. Price, Jr. - "The Reciprocal Relations of Love", 1959 April 19; 57
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0069)
  - Mozart's Requiem - conducted by Paul Young, 1959 April 26; 58
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 58, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1164)
  - Herbert Gezork - "The Dangerous Gift of Freedom"; Creighton Lacy - "The Conversions of Peter", 1959 April 26, 1959 May 03; 59
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0070)
  - Paul Scherer - "They That Wait for the Lord", 1959 May 10; 60
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0072)
  - Waldo Beach - "On Christian Consumption", 1959 May 17; 61
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0073)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "When the Cure Is a Disease", 1959 May 31; 62
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0074)
  - James A. Jones - "The Marks of Honor", 1959 June 07; 63
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0075)
  - Van Bogard Dunn - "Where to Take Hold: The Structure of the Demonic and the Structure of Grace", 1959 July 12; 64
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0076)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "The Truth in Love", 1959 September 13; 65
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0077)
  - Waldo Beach - "Where's Your Home?", 1959 September 20; 66
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0078)
  - Hugh Anderson - "The High Demands of Church Going", 1959 September 27; 67
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0079)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "No More Sea", 1959 October 11; 68
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0080)
  - Harry Philpott - "Construction Fanaticism", 1959 October 18; 69
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0081)
  - H. Shelton Smith - "This South Under God", 1959 October 25; 70
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0082)
  - William Kenneth Pope - "Years of Grace", 1959 November 01; 71
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0083)
  - McMurry S. Richey - "On Being More and Less Religious Than We Think", 1959 November 08; 72
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0084)
  - Sante Uberto Barbieri - "The Need for a New Reformation"; Bishop Paul N. Garber - "The Poor Wise Man", 1959 November 09, 1959 February 08; 73
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0064)
  - Paul Hardin, Jr. - "Let the Redeemed Say So!", 1959 November 15; 74
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0085)
  - John A. Hutchinson - "A Matter of Names", 1959 November 22; 75
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0086)
  - Robert E. Cushman - "What and Where Is Advent?", 1959 December 06; 76
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0087)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "The Nature of Christmas", 1959 December 13; 77
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0088)
  - Edmund A. Steimle - "As It Was in the Beginning", 1960 January 10; 78
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 2, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0089)
  - James L. Price, Jr. - "Taken by Surprise" Communion Meditation, 1960 January 17; 79
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0090)
  - Hugh Anderson - "Wonderful Revival", 1960 January 24; 80
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0091)
  - Waldo Beach - "On Vocational Choice", 1960 February 07; 81
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0092)
  - Elton Trueblood - "The Courage to Care", 1960 February 14; 82
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0093)
  - Stuart C. Henry - "Beyond Damascus", 1960 February 28; 83
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0094)
  - Roy A. Burkhart - "On Being a Peacemaker", 1960 March 06; 84
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0095)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Christianity and Sex", 1960 March 13; 85
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0096)
  - Waldo Beach - "Campus Crosses", 1960 March 20; 86
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0097)
  - James L. Price, Jr. - "Demonstrations in the Street and in the House of God", 1960 April 10; 87
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0098)
  - Clyde L. Manschreck - Maundy Thursday Service, 1960 April 14; 88
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0099)
  - Wilkinson, Johnson, Hyatt, O'Brian, Smith, Benedict, Shuford, and Brandenburg - Good Friday Service, 1960 April 15; 89
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0100)
  - Roland H. Bainton - Easter Service, 1960 April 17; 90
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0101)
  - Theodore O. Wedel - "Why Do I Have to Be Me?", 1960 April 24; 91
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0102)
  - Donald O. Soper - "The Christian Revolution", 1960 May 01; 92
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0103)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "The Motherhood of God", 1960 May 08; 93
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0104)
  - Hugh Anderson - "With All Thy Strength and with All Thy Mind", 1960 May 22; 94
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0105)
  - Funeral of Mary Duke Biddle, 1960 June 16; 95
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0106)
  - Hugh Anderson - "The Battle of the Soul", 1960 June 19; 96
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0107)
  - Colin Campbell - "A Mature Love of God", 1960 June 26; 97
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0108)
  - James G. Huggin - "Faith in the Future", 1960 July 03; 98
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0109)
  - Stuart C. Henry - "The Anguish of Cain", 1960 July 10; 99
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0110)
  - McMurry S. Richey - "God's Will and Ours", 1960 July 17; 100
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0111)
  - C. Roy McKay - "Christian Responsibility in a Secular Age", 1960 July 24; 101
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0112)
  - W. Arthur Kale - "A Prayer for Candidates", 1960 July 31; 102
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0113)
  - Lewis MacLachlan - Service of Holy Communion, 1960 August 07; 103
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0114)
  - Creighton Lacy - "Winds of Change in Asia", 1960 August 14; 104
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0115)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "An Educated Religion", 1960 September 18; 105
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0116)
  - James T. Cleland - "Recognition and Discovery", 1960 September 25; 106
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0117)
  - Creighton Lacy - "No Alien Race, No Foreign Shore", 1960 October 02; 107
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0118)
  - James T. Cleland - "A Christian in the World", 1960 October 09; 108
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0119)
  - Hugh Anderson - "Asking the Right Questions", 1960 October 16; 109
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0120)
  - Richard C. Raines - "Democracy in a Struggling World", 1960 October 23; 110
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0121)
  - James T. Cleland - "An Analogical Doctrine of Man", 1960 October 30; 111
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0122)
  - Harold A. Bosley - "What Are You Worth?", 1960 November 06; 112
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0123)
  - Waldo Beach - "It All Depends", 1960 November 13; 113
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 3, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0124)
  - Memorial Service for Mrs. Peyton R. Newcomb, 1960 November 16; 114